A Finding Aid to the Betty Parsons Gallery records and personal papers, circa 1920-1991, bulk 1946-1983, in the Archives of American Art AAA.parsbett
Archives of American Art
- Artists Files, 1935-1983; Series 1; (Boxes 1-18, 51, and OV 53; 17.8 linear feet)
  The files provide extensive documentation of the gallery's activities on behalf of individual artists, as well as Betty Parsons' role in the rise of Abstract Expressionism in American art and her close personal relationships with certain artists. Of particular note are the files on Jackson Pollock, Mark Rothko, Clyfford Still, and Barnett Newman, who were among the artists shown in the early years of the gallery. The Pollock file contains letters to and from the artist and his wife, Lee Krasner, as well as correspondence between Peggy Guggenheim and Parsons concerning Pollock's work and career.
  Extensive documentation can also be found on the artists Forrest Bess, William Congdon, Paul Feeley, Thomas George, Alexander Liberman, Seymour Lipton, Richard Pousette-Dart, Jesse Reichek, and Jack Youngerman. Other artists of note include Hans Hofmann, Ray Johnson, Lyman Kipp, Robert Murray, Agnes Martin, Alfonso Ossorio, Eduardo Paolozzi, Anne Ryan, Ad Reinhardt, Hans Richter, and Theodoros Stamos.
  Arrangement note
  Correspondence with artists can also be found amongst the gallery correspondence files, as well as in Betty Parsons' personal correspondence. Artists Files are arranged alphabetically by artist and further subdivided if needed by format. Files described as "General" typically include records in a wide variety of formats, such as correspondence, sales and expenses records, and shipping records.
  This series has been scanned in its entirety, except for duplicates, and slides and photographs of artwork.
  - Adams, Robert, 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Robert - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1948-1950; (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Adge, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Banerjee, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Barker, Walter - Correspondence, 1954-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barker, Walter - Price Lists, Sales, and Accounts, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Barker, Walter - Clippings, 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barker, Walter - Biographical Material, circa 1954-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barker, Walter - Announcements and Catalogs, 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Barker, Walter - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1954-1976; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Barker, Walter - Photographs, Opening, Installation, and Works in Progress, circa 1954-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bart, Robert, 1968; (Partially scanned) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bartlett, Frederic, 1943-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baynard, Ed, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bess, Forrest - Biographical Material, 1950-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bess, Forrest - Correspondence, 1946-1983; (12 folders) (Box 1, Folder 18-29)
  - Bess, Forrest - Writings by and about Artist, 1951-1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bess, Forrest - Announcements and Catalogs, 1951-1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bess, Forrest - Clippings, 1951-1982; (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 32-33)
  - Bess, Forrest - Whitney Exhibition, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bess, Forrest - Sales and Expenses, 1950-1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bess, Forrest - Contact Sheets and Negatives, Sculpture in India, 1950s; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
  - Bess, Forrest - Color Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bess, Forrest - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 39-41)
  - Bess, Forrest - Color Snapshots of Works of Art, circa 1950-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bess, Forrest - Photographs, Installations, 1962, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bess, Forrest - Snapshots by Artist, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bess, Forrest - Sketches, circa 1950-1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bigelow, Larry, 1949-1962; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 46-48)
  - Boden, Pamela, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bodin, Paul, 1959-1961; (2 folders; partially scanned) (Box 1, Folder 50-51)
  - Bodin, Paul - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1959-1961; (Not scanned) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Correspondence, 1956-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Ink Drawings, circa 1956-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1956-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1956-1981; (See also Box 51; not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Photographs, Artist, circa 1956-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bonge, Dusti - Photographs, Installations, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Box, Eden - Correspondence, 1953-1972; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
  - Box, Eden - Sales and Expenses, 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Box, Eden - Clippings, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Box, Eden - Announcements and Catalogs, 1953-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Box, Eden - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1953-1981; (Not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Box, Eden - Photographs, Artist, circa 1953-1981; (See also Box 51) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Byars, Donna, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cascella, Andrea, 1965-1980; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
  - Ceroli, Mario - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ceroli, Mario - Clippings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ceroli, Mario - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1973-1975; (Not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ceroli, Mario - Catalogs, 1972, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - General, 1970-1980; (5 folders) (Box 2, Folder 23-27)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Certificates of Authenticity (?), circa 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Price Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Color Separations and Slides, Works of Art, circa 1970-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Photograph, Artist, circa 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1970-1980; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Clippings and Publications, 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Chase-Riboud, Barbara - Clippings and Publications, Duplicates, 1966-1973; (Not scanned) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - de Chirico, Giorgio, 1948-1957; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Christoffersen, Frede, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chryssa - Biographical Material, circa 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Chryssa - Correspondence, 1958-1964; (See also OV 53) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chryssa - Sales, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Chryssa - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1960-1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Chryssa - Photographs, Installation, circa 1962 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Clendenin, Eve, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Bernard - General, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Bernard - Slides and Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1964-1968; (Not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Bernard - Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Bernard - Catalogs, 1961-1972; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
  - Congdon, William - Biographical Material, circa 1948-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Congdon, William - Autobiographical Writings, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Congdon, William - Statements on Art, 1952-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Congdon, William - Writings on Artist and Other Writings, circa 1948-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Congdon, William - Writings by Artist, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Congdon, William - Miscellaneous Exhibition Material, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Congdon, William - General, 1948-1983; (27 folders) (Box 3, Folder 14-40)
  - Congdon, William - Price Lists, 1950-1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Congdon, William - Sales Record, circa 1948-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Congdon, William - Inventory Records, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Congdon, William - Announcements, 1949-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Congdon, William - Catalogs, 1953-1983; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 5-7)
  - Congdon, William - Clippings, circa 1950-1970; (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 8-11)
  - Congdon, William - Other Printed Material, 1953-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Congdon, William - Photographs, Artist, circa 1948-1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Congdon, William - Photographs, Installations, circa 1948-1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Congdon, William - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1948-1983; (9 folders; not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 15-23)
  - Congdon, William - Photographs, "Works for Sale", circa 1948-1983; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Congdon, William - Negatives, Works of Art, circa 1948-1983; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Congdon, William - Color Reproductions of Art Work, circa 1948-1983; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cooke, Kathleen - Biographical Material, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cooke, Kathleen - General, 1969-1975; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
  - Cooke, Kathleen - Price Lists, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Cooke, Kathleen - Clippings, 1969-1973; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 31-32)
  - Cooke, Kathleen - Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cornell, Joseph, 1948-1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dante, Giglio - General, 1944-1951; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 35-36)
  - Dante, Giglio - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1944-1951; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Dante, Giglio - Clippings, Announcements, and Price Lists, 1945-1949 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Davidson, Carol Kreeger, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Dienes, Sari - General, 1952-1959; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 40-41)
  - Dienes, Sari - Announcements and Catalogs, 1950-1959 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Dienes, Sari - Clippings, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Dienes, Sari - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1952-1959; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Donati, Enrico - General, 1946-1965; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
  - Donati, Enrico - Photographs, Installation, circa 1946-1965 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Donati, Enrico - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1946-1965; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Donati, Enrico - Clippings, 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Donati, Enrico - Announcements and Catalogs, 1958-1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Donati, Enrico - Announcements and Catalogs, Duplicates, 1958-1979; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dorr, William, undated; (Partially scanned) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Evans, John, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Falkenstein, Claire, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Falkenstein, Claire - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1952-1958; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Feeley, Paul - Biographical Material, circa 1960-1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Feeley, Paul - General, 1959-1980; (8 folders) (Box 5, Folder 9-16)
  - Feeley, Paul - Price Lists and Summary of Sales, 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Feeley, Paul - Catalog Essay by E. C. Goossen, circa 1960-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Feeley, Paul - Snapshots, Artist and Friends, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Feeley, Paul - Photographs, Installations, circa 1960-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Feeley, Paul - Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1960-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Feeley, Paul - Photographs, Works of Art (1954-1965), circa 1960-1980; (9 folders; not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 22-30)
  - Feeley, Paul - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1960-1980; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 31-32)
  - Feeley, Paul - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1960-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Feeley, Paul - Printer's Plates, circa 1960-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Feeley, Paul - Announcements, 1960-1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Feeley, Paul - Catalogs, 1962-1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Feeley, Paul - A Selection of Critical Reviews for "Art of the Real", 1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Feeley, Paul - Clippings, 1962-1975; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - Ferber, Herbert, 1947-1955; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 40-42)
  - Ferguson, Claire, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Fernandez, Augustin, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Fernandez, Augustin - Photographs, Works of Art, 1967-1970; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Fimpel, Vernon, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Fimpel, Vernon - Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1968-1969; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Fine, Perle - General, 1948-1954 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Fine, Perle - Announcements and Clippings, 1947-1951 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Fine, Perle - Photographs, Artist, circa 1950 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Fine, Perle - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1948-1954; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Fischel, Marguerite, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Freedberg, Albert, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Freemantle, Chloe, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fritzius, Harry, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gear, William - Correspondence, 1944-1950 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gear, William - General, circa 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gear, William - Photographs, 1949; (Partially scanned) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gego, 1970-1972; (2 folders; partially scanned) (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - Geitlinger, Ernst, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Geitlinger, Ernst - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1949-1950; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - George, Thomas - Biographical Material and Writings, circa 1960-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - George, Thomas - Biographical Material and Writings, Duplicates, circa 1960-1980; (Not Scanned) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - George, Thomas - Correspondence, 1959-1981; (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 18-23)
  - George, Thomas - Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1981; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
  - George, Thomas - Sales and Expenses, 1959-1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - George, Thomas - Price Lists, 1963-1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - George, Thomas - Photographs, Installations, 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - George, Thomas - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1960-1980; (6 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 29-34)
  - George, Thomas - Color Transparencies, Works of Art, circa 1960-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - George, Thomas - Clippings and Other Printed Material, 1959-1978; (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 36-41)
  - George, Thomas - Clippings and Other Printed Material, Duplicates, 1959-1978; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - George, Thomas - Publicity, Norwegian Exhibition, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Gillen, Michael - General, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Gillen, Michael - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1968-1971; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 45-48)
  - Godwin, Judith, 1959-1981 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Godwin, Judith - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1959-1960; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Goodwin, John, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Gray, Cleve, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Guerrero, Jose - General, 1954-1963; (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 53-55)
  - Guerrero, Jose - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1954-1964 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Guerrero, Jose - Photograph, Artist, circa 1954-1963 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Guerrero, Jose - Photographs, Installations, circa 1954-1963 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Guerrero, Jose - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1954-1963; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Guston, Phillip, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hales, Dorothy (collector), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Biographical Material and Price Lists, 1969-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Correspondence, 1954-1982; (10 folders) (Box 7, Folder 4-13)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Writings, 1957-1975; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Sales and Expenses, 1958-1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Lists of Works, circa 1954-1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Inventory Cards, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Announcements and Catalogs, 1955-1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Clippings, 1958-1973; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 20-22)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Information Supplied by the Artist about Individual Works of Art, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Slides, Works of Art, circa 1954-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1954-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Color Separations, Works of Art, circa 1954-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hamblett, Theora - Photographs, Artist, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hawkins, John Franklin, 1943-1944; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
  - Hawkins, John Franklin - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1943-1944; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hayter, Stanley William, 1944-1945; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
  - Hayter, Stanley William - Photographs, Works of Art, 1944-1945; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Heller, Dorothy, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hennessey, Timothy - General, 1963-1972; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 35-37)
  - Hennessey, Timothy - Sales, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hennessey, Timothy - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hennessey, Timothy - Photographs, Robes Designed by Artist, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hoff, Margo, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hofmann, Hans - General, 1944-1947; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 42-44)
  - Hofmann, Hans - Announcements and Catalogs, 1944-1981 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Hofmann, Hans - Clippings, 1943-1963 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Hofmann, Hans - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1944-1947; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 47-48)
  - Howell, Douglass, 1954-1955; (Partially scanned) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Hugo, Jean - General, 1971-1976; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 50-51)
  - Hugo, Jean - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Hugo, Jean - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1971-1976; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Hugo, Jean - Photographs, Artist, circa 1972 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Huyck, Laura Talmage, 1955-1966; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 55-56)
  - Huyck, Laura Talmage - Photographs, circa 1955-1966; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Jackson, Jean Jones - General, 1966-1979; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Jackson, Jean Jones - Announcements and Clippings, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, Jean Jones - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1966-1979; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 5-7)
  - Jackson, Jean Jones - Photographs, Artist, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jacobsen, Jurgen, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Buffie, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Buffie - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1950-1952; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Ray - General, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Ray - Clippings, 1964-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Ray - Announcements and Catalogs, 1968-1975; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - Johnson, Ray - Photographs, Works of Art, 1970s; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
  - Johnson, Ray - Sketch, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Ray - Photograph, Installation, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, William H., 1943-1944, 1973; (partially scanned) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Kabak, Robert, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kabak, Robert - Photographs and Slides, Works of Art, 1965-1967; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth - Catalogue, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Kent, Adaline - General, 1948-1977; (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 24-27)
  - Kent, Adaline - Slides, Installations, circa 1948-1977; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Kent, Adaline - Announcements, Catalogs, and Book Cover, 1949-1957 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Kent, Adaline - Clippings, 1948-1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Kent, Adaline - Photographs, Artist's Studio, 1950s; (See Box 51) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Kent, Adaline - Photographs, Artist, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Kent, Adaline - Photographs, Installations, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Kent, Adaline - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1948-1977; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Biographical Material, circa 1954-1983 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kipp, Lyman - General, 1954-1983; (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 37-40)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Price Lists, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Announcements and Catalogs, 1954-1971; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Clippings, 1956-1968; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 44-46)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Photographs, Artist, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Photographs, "Old Works", circa 1954-1983; (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 48-51)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Photographs, "Works Sold", circa 1948-1983; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Photographs, Recent Works of Art, 1960s; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Snapshots, Works of Art, 1962; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Kipp, Lyman - Reproductions, Works of Art, 1970s; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Knoop, Guitou, 1935-1950; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Knoop, Guitou - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1947; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Koehler, Henry - General, 1971-1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Koehler, Henry - Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1979; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Koehler, Henry - Clippings, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Koehler, Henry - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1971-1980; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Krasner, Lee, 1949-1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Krasner, Lee - Reproductions of Works of Art, circa 1950s; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - Biographical Material, circa 1947-1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - General, 1947-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - Clippings and Announcements, 1955-1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - Photographs, Artist, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - Snapshots and Slides, Works of Art, circa 1947-1974; (Glass slide is cracked; not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lazzari, Pietro - Photographs, Works of Art, 1960s; (5 folders; not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 20-24)
  - Lee, Amy Freeman - General, 1949-1952; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Lee, Amy Freeman - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1947-1950 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Lee, Amy Freeman - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1949-1952 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Biographical Material, circa 1960-1979 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Correspondence, 1960-1979; (5 folders) (Box 9, Folder 30-34)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Hand-Screened Christmas Card, circa 1960-1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Exhibition Guest List, circa 1960-1979 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Price Lists, 1960-1972 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Appraisals, Sales, and Expenses, 1960-1976; (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 38-40)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Press Releases, circa 1960-1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Publicity, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Photographs, Works of Art, 1960s; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Photographs, Installations, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1982; (5 folders) (Box 9, Folder 45-49)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Clippings, 1960-1974; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 50-53)
  - Liberman, Alexander - Miscellaneous Catalog Material, 1960-1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Liebman, Marjorie - General, 1952-1962; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Liebman, Marjorie - Clippings, Announcements, and Catalogs, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Liebman, Marjorie - Photographs, Installations, circa 1952-1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Liebman, Marjorie - Photographs, Works of Art, circa 1952-1962; (Not scanned) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lindner, Richard - Biographical Material, 1950s (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Lindner, Richard - General, 1954-1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)